<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concept-rsses on l&#39;eau&#39;s gdd</title>
    <link>https://louisgv.github.io/leau.doc/concept/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concept-rsses on l&#39;eau&#39;s gdd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://louisgv.github.io/leau.doc/concept/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept</title>
      <link>https://louisgv.github.io/leau.doc/concept/base/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://louisgv.github.io/leau.doc/concept/base/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;concept&#34;&gt;Concept&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;images/concepts/keysword0.png&#34; alt=&#34;Keywords Note 0&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are more than 1.2 billion people lacking access to clean drinking water in the world, but only a handful of organization and billionaire are looking to solve this problem. In order to inspire a solution to such a geographic-specific problem, there need a culture movement, and it must be artful first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;L&amp;rsquo;eau&lt;/strong&gt; is an adventure game that tells the origin story of a &lt;em&gt;water deity&lt;/em&gt; set in a fictional world where water is so rare, it is both a currency and a major spiritual concept.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By showing how the creature in this world can appreciate water capitally as well as spiritually, the game hope to inspire such level of appreciation within the player, especially the youth. For man must appreciate the simplest thing in life before he can cherish life to its fullest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;aside class=&#34;admonition note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;admonition-title&#34;&gt;Motivation&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Showing appreciation toward water, something often taken for granted in first-world countries. Hopefully the game will inspire further philanthropic action toward solving the global clean water crisis.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concept</title>
      <link>https://louisgv.github.io/leau.doc/concept/target-audience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://louisgv.github.io/leau.doc/concept/target-audience/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;target-audience&#34;&gt;Target Audience&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Journey is an indie video game developed by thatgamecompany and published by Sony Coputer Entertainment for the PlayStation 3. In Journey, the player controls a robed figure in a vast desert, traveling towards a mountain in the distance. Other players on the same journey can be discovered, and two players can meet and assist each other, but they cannot communicate via speech or text and cannot see each other&amp;rsquo;s names. It is listed as one of the greatest games of all time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those who enjoy &lt;em&gt;Journey&lt;/em&gt; will find this game somewhat familiar. However, &lt;em&gt;L&amp;rsquo;eau&lt;/em&gt; push the boundary of artful game further by introducing a more diverse range of culture as well as habitat. &lt;em&gt;L&amp;rsquo;eau&lt;/em&gt; is more about &lt;em&gt;exploration&lt;/em&gt;, building &lt;em&gt;relationship&lt;/em&gt;, learning about the &lt;em&gt;economy&lt;/em&gt; and enjoying the flow state rather than going toward an end goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;aside class=&#34;admonition note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;admonition-title&#34;&gt;L&amp;#39;eau&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;is a thoughtful artistic game that seeks to inspire player emotionally and intellectually.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>