<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Gameplay-rsses on l&#39;eau&#39;s gdd</title>
    <link>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Gameplay-rsses on l&#39;eau&#39;s gdd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Gameplay</title>
      <link>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/base/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/base/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h1 id=&#34;gameplay&#34;&gt;Gameplay&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All in all, &lt;strong&gt;contents&lt;/strong&gt; matter. The more content placed at the right place that pique the interest of player, then regardless of who the player is, they will always want to explore the world. As there is something to explore, not just a long walk toward the end, where they already expect the end goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, human was not aware of the bidirectional thought (i.e, you can show them a goal with 2 consequences, and they wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want to guess it). But now in a world where entertainment is so popular, human has soon adapted such that they understand how to interpret the event and the goal and they know what final choice they will have eventually. There is no ending that is too foreign to our player. To patch this, some choose to mislead the player, some choose to have non-binary goal, some choose to do some novel thing, and some try a combination of stuffs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game is at heart an adventure, exploration game. There are several element that achieve this, and in order to avoid the dry feeling of repetitive that many adventure game does, which failed to capture the interest of the hyper audience we have today, there must be a combination of element within the adventure genre to craft a successful one. A plain one where player go from A to B will not work!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Traveling added with Spontaneous (with a chance of happening) events with funky random NPCs (that are contents which serve future purpose).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Background events, far away signal, the concept of using the environment as our HUD.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actions with consequences and also lead the player toward foreign landmark.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Introducing out-of-norm culture and behaviors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;aside class=&#34;admonition warning-a&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&#34;admonition-title&#34;&gt;L&amp;#39;eau is an adventure game&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;that entertains and pique the player&amp;rsquo;s interest each and every seconds!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/aside&gt;

</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Objectives</title>
      <link>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/objectives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/objectives/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;objectives&#34;&gt;Objectives&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To become a &lt;code&gt;water deity&lt;/code&gt;, the player main job is of course to deliver water to those who are needing it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are several type of Objectives in the game:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Transporting water from place to place&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going to landmark to get water&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;

&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Going back to where you was to give back the water&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Either stay there for the fun, or return for the objectives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game demonstrate the traveler dilemma. Would you return to your home land to give them the water (albeit the travel back), or would you keep on exploring the world ahead?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This  might sounds linear somewhat. We need a way to expand this such that the player doesn&amp;rsquo;t serve just a single village, but multiple of them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The big question here is, given that the upcoming adventure will be mesmerizing and entertaining, will the player remember their original objective?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We must faintly make the original objective something the player might or might not remember.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The act of give and take creates an economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The act of asking to give and take creates generosity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There will be some that you can give water to who do not request for it. Your job however, is to give them the water.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By promising bigger reward, and giving the player more visual entertainment, we can misled them into going with the flow and thus make them go forward, misguiding that this is an A to B game, but instead for any direction they go forward, they only experience part of the game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last economy?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How to show the player what they can possibly achieve?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There must be a way where player cross-path with their previous quest, where they would eventually learn that it would be &lt;code&gt;too late&lt;/code&gt; to do so!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The player are guided and given multiple choice to deliver water across this world, but everytime they get the water, more promise of more water on the land ahead, and further greed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The player must make their choice to return and florish their previous.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timeline for this must be catered such that it will be a trade-off. All being in this world has a timespan in days to live.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The timespan must be designed such that they player can revisit them eventually.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Path crossing between quests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There must be more than 3 ways of choosing choice. Right now I can think of three way the player are designed to play this game. Let&amp;rsquo;s say they need to deliver water from B to A, and they started at A.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, when they came to B, the people at B says that there is more water at C, and they only have some water left. The water left is enough for travel back to A and flourish A, if they choose to do so. Or they can use half the water to go toward C.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is somewhat illogical. But somehow, it does serve a certain purpose. Now given that the player decided to go back to A and help A, what happens to B and C?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The B landmark must have more reasoning or something demanding such that they misled player to go toward C instead for the water for both A and B.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Player are tricked to Stack their quest.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many landmark will we have? Let&amp;rsquo;s say we have 9 landmarks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each move has a consequence, similar to a peg game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually they will go toward the Tropical land, where water run amok.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When will they cross path with A again given they chose to abandon it? (To show them the consequence).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The landmark A must be somewhat simple, but something that can immediately aid players&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the way, player can give water to creature such that they will let player &lt;code&gt;ride&lt;/code&gt; them for extra speed. There are two penalty when coming up with this:
  * If player did not return to give the first Lama at A the water, then all Horse will have very low speed
  * Or they will need to feed more water to the creature before they can ride them&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to war for water?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Challenges</title>
      <link>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/challenges/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;challenges&#34;&gt;Challenges&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Choosing between goals and objectives and figuring out/remembering their benefit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;As the story move on, there will be point where the player must choose between multiple objectives in order to maximize their current status and speed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;L&amp;rsquo;eau adopts the newgame+ strategy to allow for near endless playing loop, letting user try different way of play without losing too much progress.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Every events in the game cost a time unit, and the user consume the time unit by traveling or by sleeping over the time period.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Managing time&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Controls</title>
      <link>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/controls/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/controls/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;controls&#34;&gt;Controls&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Movement Analog&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rotation Analog or L/R triggers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Accept/Action button&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cancel/Drop button&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Info button&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jump button&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rewards</title>
      <link>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/rewards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://gdd.lnp.moe/leau/gameplay/rewards/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;rewards&#34;&gt;Rewards&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ability:
  + Animal rider (by feeding water to enough animal of a certain type)
  +&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Events&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Random Event Chance Increased&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Story&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hidden routes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Point in relationship graphs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Water source and economy around the map&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>